[ "Hey Man. Nice Shot" plays ]
[ Horns honking ]
♪ I wish I would have met you
♪ now it's a little late
♪ what you
could have taught me ♪
♪ I could have saved some face
[ horns honking ]
♪ They think
that your early ending ♪
♪ was all wrong
[ indistinct shouting ]
[ Horn honks ]
♪ Hey. man!
♪ Nice shot
[ Engine revving ]
♪ Hey. man!
[ Computer beeps ]
[ Beep ]
[ Beeping ]
Man: The plan failed.
We can't decode the message.
Call Raymond Reddington.
Sync by GeirDM
www.addic7ed.com
[ door creaks ]
[ Birds chirping ]
[ Garbage truck approaches ]
[ Brakes squeal ]
[ Engine idling ]
[ Engine revs. beeping ]
[ Muffled gunshot ]
[ Children playing ]
- From Wujing.
- Good God. Not here.
The gentleman I usually
contract with is unavailable --
stung by a Manta Ray
off the barrier reef in Belize.
[ Chuckles ]
I have another tech in mind.
This needs to be done quickly.
- Today? - Speak with Luli about
the replacement I'm offering.
Conduct your due diligence.
If things are in order.
we can proceed as discussed.
I prefer to play with myself
in private.
Tom: Are you okay?
Yeah. sorry.
I'm just a little distracted.
No. that's --
that's all right.
I'm...sitting here talking about
what happened to me
like it only happened to me.
But it happened to us both.
It's just a little weird
to be home because...
Lizzy.
a man came into our home.
I know. I'm sorry.
I wish I could tell you more.
I want to tell you more.
I --
So. tell me something.
Who was he?
He's gone.
He was killed.
So it's over?
Yes.
Look. I love you.
[ Knock on door ]
That's Ellie.
I just hate that there are
things you have to hide from me.
Good morning!
Hope you're hungry.
I'm making breakfast.
Oh. you don't have to do that.
Are you kidding?
A good omelet
has healing powers.
Bruce and Melissa are
bringing over dinner tonight.
That's incredibly cool of you.
Hey. friends
don't let friends starve
when they've been stabbed
by violent psychopaths.
[ Chuckles ]
How's he doing?
I'm sitting right here.
I'm not asking you.
You'll say fine.
because that's what you do.
You're a good actor.
Karen's covering my classes.
We're gonna eat and then
head over to physical therapy.
I got to run.
Ellie. we owe you.
So true.
You know I wouldn't go
if I didn't have to.
Look. whatever
they pulled you into.
the sooner you get it over with.
the sooner we get our life back.
Okay.
Bye.
[ Door opens. closes ]
[ Birds chirping ]
[ Car door closes ]
Slug and casing
from a 9-millimeter.
Can you run these
and see if they match
any crimes in our system?
[ Bell jingles ]
An opportunity
has come our way.
Yesterday. the Chinese killed
a C.I.A. agent in Shanghai.
They took his computer.
which they thought could decode
a message they intercepted.
It couldn't.
They've asked me to help.
Oh. Rodrick
is a dear old friend.
I'm sorry.
You're decoding C.I.A. messages
on behalf of the Chinese?
Now. you see. you make it sound
like treason.
So black and white.
It's not. It's green.
The fact is.
American secrets are for sale
by an assortment of reputable
vendors. myself included.
If I don't do this.
someone else will.
The man who's paying me
is called Wujing.
Perhaps you've heard of him.
Formerly. he worked for
the Ministry of State Security.
He's not officially sanctioned
by the Chinese.
But unofficially.
he's contracted
to take out rival agents --
American. British.
The message likely contains
the name of another agent.
Do you expect me
to believe that --
a secret meeting
with the mysterious Wujing?
Intriguing. isn't it?
He's a myth.
That's what they said about
deep throat and the G-spot.
I assure you Wujing is
quite real. and he's hired me.
Now you have the chance
to catch him.
I've already forwarded them
your cover.
What? What cover?
Carolyn Givins.
PhD in Applied Physics
from M.I.T.
I've told them you're
my new encryption specialist.
You're asking me to betray
the life of an American agent.
Listen. this is a guy
who the intelligence community
has been talking about
for decades
as if he were a figment.
You don't even know
if he's real or not.
Well. he is real --
very.
And I'm giving you
the opportunity to grab him.
Now. the good news is
he's not even in China.
He's right here
in your own backyard.
If we play our cards right.
I can still make Lisbon
by breakfast.
Rodrick. both.
Meera: Michael Alvarado.
Kevin Wyatt. Bryce Jensen --
three agents based in China.
three covers blown.
According to Reddington.
all were murdered
by a man named Wujing.
Who is Wujing?
China has a one-child policy.
They say that Wujing
was a second child.
So they gave him away.
denied he was ever born.
He was invisible to his family.
Wujing made a life
working in a business
where invisibility
was an incredible asset.
Reddington's told you
he can find this guy?
He claims Wujing has hired him
to decode a message
that the Chinese have
intercepted from the C.I.A.
He believes that it might
contain the identify
of another one of our assets
in China.
I think we should move on this.
I'm not prepared to do this.
I understand
you have reservations.
Reservations?
You're asking me to spy
on a notorious spy killer
while pretending to be
an expert in cryptography.
which I know nothing about.
Reddington insists on you.
I'm sorry.
Look at those pictures.
If there is a name
in that message.
there's gonna be another face
in that file.
That'll be on you.
[ Indistinct conversation ]
[ Chuckles ]
[ "Bird" plays ]
[ Bird squawks ]
♪ There is one bird
in my house ♪
♪ she said you woke up
from a dream ♪
♪ he heard Mama Cass.
he felt better ♪
♪ if I would have known
those things ♪
[ Drill whirs ]
[ Camera shutter clicking ]
Ellie: I'll be back in a second.
I just need to grab my purse.
I thought
it was on the counter.
Hello?
Tom: Hey.
Did you find it?
Oh. yeah. sorry.
I'm coming.
Okay. Say I do this.
What's in it for me?
Look at you.
camel trading like a bedouin.
If I'm gonna help you.
I want something in return.
Such as?
The truth. Just once.
I want to know
why you chose me.
Well. then.
we need to move quickly.
Things are already in play.
WDCJ -- a small radio station
five miles from here.
The building was purchased
six years ago
by a corporation fronting
for the Chinese government.
Ressler:
I'm sorry. Wait.
You're telling us that
Wujing is running a spy ring
out of a radio station?
[ Laughing ]
We'll meet Wujing.
You'll decode the message
and transmit it to your team.
If I decode the message.
that means
the Chinese get it. too.
Exactly --
both you and the Chinese
will know the name of the agent
for which the message
was intended.
and the race begins.
We try to save him.
The Chinese try to kill him.
We could give them a false message.
No.
That could work.
We could send them in the wrong direction.
I said no.
The Chinese may not know
what the message is.
but they certainly know
what it isn't.
We do it for real.
or we don't do it at all.
Great plan. except.
as I have said.
I know nothing
about encryption.
You're a very quick study.
I have a guy
who can help you with that.
[ Speaking Mandarin ]
The Chinese will give you
an intercepted message
on one of these.
Insert it. and it will prompt
you to connect a data locker.
Shun Lee says
it's like a magic box.
A magic box?
[ Speaking Mandarin ]
The data locker applies a key
to the message.
It'll take a moment.
but the decoded message
will appear on your laptop.
How do I get the message out?
You don't.
The computer does it for you.
All you need is
a satellite connection.
[ Speaking Mandarin ]
If you don't have a satellite
connection. use this.
It's a remote
mirroring program.
It'll give our tech on the
outside control of the system.
It's gonna be okay.
[ Speaking Mandarin ]
Great.
You're rocking the Mandarin.
Xiè xie.
Three minutes
till the meeting. sir.
Where the hell is Reddington?
He's late.
He's gonna blow this whole damn thing.
Do you smoke?
No.
Well. you do now.
Or at least
you're trying to quit.
This is C.I.A. equipment.
It's brand-new.
It looks like a nicotine patch.
but it's a very sensitive
transmitter.
It has a range of 300 yards.
and it's a plastic polymer.
which means it won't show up
if it gets wanded.
And if you're wrong?
I'm not wrong.
Where the hell is he? He was
supposed to be here an hour --
What are we waiting for?
Surveillance One.
are you in position?
Roger that. In position.
Satellite feed up and running.
Right this way.
Here we go.
Sorry. sir. Protocol.
Miss. please.
[ Static ]
Thank you. Sir?
[ Beep ]
DARPA tracking chip.
8-millimeter tag.
I was taken by Somali pirates
last March.
spent three weeks
in a shipping container.
The first two were a nightmare.
The third one
was actually quite pleasant.
Even so.
that won't happen again.
[ Beep ]
If you have a clean razor blade
and some morphine.
I'll remove it.
That won't be necessary.
but I am going to need
a biometric print scan
from your associate.
She's with me.
Understood.
But my orders are
to scan any new visitors.
What database
is this being run against?
All of them.
[ Beep ]
[ Keyboard clacking ]
Ressler: What's happening?
They are running her prints.
Can you intercept them?
I don't know.
So. you went with the gray?
Okay.
Vanish.
[ Beep ]
Follow me.
As you can see.
we've made some improvements.
Oh. your DARPA chip won't work
where you're going.
Wujing will explain
when you get there.
Get where?
[ Beeping ]
What the hell just happened?
- We lost them. - We can't just lose them.
What happened to our signal?
They seem to be descending.
which doesn't make any sense.
The blueprints don't show
any underground space.
Get that signal back.
How far down
do you think we're going?
Far enough.
My friend.
Don't be cheeky. Wujing.
You don't have any friends.
My associate.
Ms. Givins.
Professor Robins
only works with the best.
Oh. he was an amazing teacher.
I was so sorry to hear
that he passed away.
You've made some changes.
We had to increase security.
I can imagine --
four American agents killed
in the past year and a half.
You've been busy.
I presume
nothing gets in or out.
no radio
or satellite transmissions.
Nothing but trust.
Please don't take offense.
I can't risk
American surveillance.
Only our systems are hard-wired
to the outside world.
Let's get to work.
I once had a bad experience
in a deep hole in the ground.
Wujing: Jin Sun.
my new senior cryptographer.
We expected
standard RSA encryption.
but this was
something stronger.
The government's
been experimenting
with better
factoring algorithms.
It's only a matter of time
before RSA's obsolete.
You're right. It is.
I'll just need a few moments
to set up my equipment.
This way.
Meera: They're trying.
but still nothing.
Either the Chinese
are scrambling our signals.
or Liz and Red
are out of range.
I thought your equipment
had a range of 300 yards.
It does. but maybe they've built
a bunker that deep
under the building.
We're getting played.
That signal went dark because
Red and Liz wanted it to.
That's not likely.
How long
can we wait to find out?
Is it possible
they could be in danger?
That's another reason
not to wait.
Keep all insertion teams
on standby.
If we don't hear from Agent Keen
in five minutes. we're going in.
[ Indistinct conversations ]
We ready yet?
Do you get home much. Jin Sun?
Not for two years.
Oh. that must be hard.
It certainly would be for me.
I don't even have a phone.
I insist on delivering
all of my messages in person.
What province are you from?
From Yunnan.
Oh. beautiful part
of the country.
I spent a month
in silent meditation
at a monastery
just outside of Kunming.
It was a wonderful escape
from the distractions
of everyday life.
I can't imagine the distractions
one might encounter down here.
Can you?
No. I can't.
Excellent.
I think we're almost ready.
This should be fun.
What the hell is that?
I swear. if I run
into the same trouble
I had with you in Hong Kong...
In all the years
you and I have known each other.
I've never put you
in a position like this.
You know how I conduct
my business.
I don't need this kind of crap.
You assured me
this place was secure.
It is.
Then what the hell is that?!
That van.
It was there when we arrived.
and it's still there.
That is the FBI.
With all the scans and wands
and this elevator you've built
that goes down to middle earth.
and you don't even bother
to sweep the street
around your building?
This is nonsense.
Calm down. old friend.
You're under surveillance!
If the FBI was outside.
it's because you led them here.
I've been moving comfortably
through the world
for the past 20 years
without a trace.
and now
some two-bit spy killer
is gonna put my life
and business in jeopardy?
[ Speaking Mandarin ]
We have activity.
Everybody. heads up.
We're made. Your 2:00.
Break it down. 15 seconds.
We got to go.
Pack it up.
Man: You!
¿Qué pasa?
[ Scoffs ]
They know we're here.
Maybe.
Or maybe the van's just been there
too long and they're being careful.
I don't like it.
We're going in on my signal.
[ Indistinct conversations ]
[ Receiver clicks ]
Unbelievable.
You see? Nothing.
Now...can we continue?
You should be ashamed
of yourself.
To put Ms. Givins and I at risk.
it's unprofessional.
I've reached my limit.
Enough!
What?
Okay. Okay.
You know. I'm sorry.
[ Chuckling ]
I've had a rough day.
Unbelievable.
[ Claps hands ]
Should we do this?
[ Radio chatter ] Let's roll.
E.T.A. -- one minute.
[ Engine turns over.
tires screeching ]
The message.
[ Beeping ]
Red: Don't you miss
the good old days
with the pay phones
and the brush passes?
Man: 30 seconds out.
[ Beeping ]
Wait. I've got something.
She's using
the remote mirroring program
Meera's contact gave her.
Uh. hang on.
This isn't her computer.
It looks like
one of the Chinese systems.
Can you see
the C.I.A. message?
Uh. yes. sir. and a lot more
than that. Downloading now.
Man: 10 seconds out.
Okay. All units -- stand down.
[ Siren chirps ]
I repeat. stand down.
I repeat. all units stand down.
Standing down.
[ Beep ]
There's your next target --
kill number five.
Henry Cho.
We have the message.
The target is Henry Cho.
All right. The clock is ticking. I want
everything we can find on this guy.
Liz: This was sent
from a C.I.A. server.
delivered to a server
at the Nanjing Grand Hotel.
So. Mr. Cho. why is the C.I.A.
sending you secret messages
at your hotel?
Ressler: Hold on.
This guy's not an agent.
He's Chinese-American.
an architect.
An architect?
Then why the hell is
he talking to the C.I.A.?
Because we asked for his help.
Jin Sun: Henry Cho works
for Zhongku Construction.
Not in China. here in D.C.
Zhongku -- they're
a huge construction company.
They design buildings
all over the world.
His immigration file says he's
been to the company headquarters
6 times in the last 10 months.
Meera: That's why the C.I.A.
reached out to him.
Zhongku's designing a new
government building in Shanghai.
We asked Henry to use his access
to get us the plans.
Thanks to him. our ops bugged
the entire city
military commission.
Let me get this straight.
This guy's not
a trained operative.
He's just a...contractor?
A civilian.
Where is he now?
Aram: Here.
Immigration says
he left China three days ago.
a return flight
to Dulles airport.
Thank you. Aram.
You're welcome.
[ Keyboard clacks ]
Go get him.
Woman: Zhongku Construction.
Henry Cho. please.
It's very important that
I speak to him immediately.
His brother. Xiaoping.
has been in a car accident.
He's at our Fairview property
with his son.
I can try to call him --
[ Speaking Mandarin ]
There's no answer on his cell.
Call the company.
Find out where he is.
[ Engine turns over ]
[ Tires screech ]
My friend.
I can't thank you enough.
This is all the thanks
I require.
Get your things.
It's time to go.
Leave it.
[ Alarm beeping ]
Wujing: Lock it down.
Stop!
[ Buzzer sounds ]
[ Gate clangs ]
[ Sighs ]
You were right.
Maybe that was the FBI outside.
In fact.
maybe they're not just outside.
Maybe they're right here
in this room.
Think hard before you accuse
anybody of anything.
A few minutes ago.
contact was made from this room
to an FBI server.
A message I worked so hard
to intercept
was sent to the Americans.
Well. all my instincts
said it was her.
I trust my instincts.
You're smart.
The one responsible was smart.
but our systems are smarter.
Any contact with a government
server is flagged for review.
So...
I know who betrayed us.
[ Both grunting ]
[ Tires screech ]
He's not at the office.
He's with a client at a property
at Fairview and Wallace.
Try him again.
So. over here.
they're gonna make some windows.
And out here...
there's gonna be a balcony that runs
the length of the whole build--
you said we were gonna get ice cream.
[ Laughing ] Okay.
[ Cellphone vibrating ]
Let me just show you something else first.
Wujing: Get him up.
[ Groaning ]
I thought you were loyal to us.
I don't understand.
The message was sent
from your system. Jin Sun.
T-that's not possible.
Yeah. yeah. yeah.
Hey. hey. hey!
That's not possible.
It is.
and not just one message.
You gave them everything.
files we've worked on
for months!
Nobody else had access.
We have to do something.
Quiet.
[ Coughing ]
We can't just let them do this.
[ Speaking Mandarin ]
You --
As entertaining
as all this has been.
we really do need to leave now.
The next sound you hear
is gonna be the FBI
knocking on your door.
and I. for one.
am not gonna be here.
Wujing! Look at me!
You don't kill
one of my people.
Now I have to kill
one of yours.
The moment he sent that message.
he became worthless to you.
You would have beaten him
for another 20 minutes
and then killed him yourself.
But if I let you kill
a contractor of mine.
I'll lose the trust
of all my others.
and that's just bad business.
So if you kill her.
you better kill me.
Or I'm going to kill you.
You hired me to do a job.
It's done.
Now let's get out of here.
Follow me.
I have another way out.
Let's go get you
some ice cream. all right?
Okay.
[ Cellphone vibrating ]
[ Beep ]
Hello?
Mr. Cho. this is Agent Meera Malik
with the C.I.A.
C.I.A.?
I don't understand.
You're not supposed to be
calling me on this line.
Listen to me.
You are in danger.
Can you hear me?
The Chinese have your name.
There are men on their way
to your location.
We're on the 12th floor.
Stay where you are. We're coming to get you.
Stay hidden.
We're just minutes out.
[ Elevator whirring ]
Boy: Dad?
Come here.
Come here. Let's go.
Wujing: I've been building
this place for three years.
and now my operation is burned.
So build another.
Aram:
Sir. I've got them.
The microchip in Red's neck
just came online
and the bug we put
on Agent Keen.
They're out of the building.
moving west on Danforth.
Where the hell are they going?
Just send agents
to intercept them.
[ Hard hat clatters ]
[ Indistinct shouting
in distance ]
Get underneath.
Listen. Listen.
Don't move. all right?
Just don't move.
No. put your hand in.
Shh! Shh! Shh!
[ Elevator whirring ]
[ Indistinct shouting ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Gunshots ]
[ Bone cracks ]
[ Screams ]
[ Indistinct shouting ]
Ow!
No!
Stop! Dad!
Dad! Dad! Dad! Dad!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Let him go! Let my son go!
Please! Please!
Just let my son go! Please!
It's gonna be okay. It's gonna be okay.
I'll do anything.
[ Both grunting ]
Just let him go.
It's gonna be all right.
It's gonna be all right. I promise. I promise.
Dad!
[ Gunshots ]
Meera: Ressler. clear!
Ressler. clear?
I'm good. Thanks.
[ Breathing heavily ]
Thank you.
Thank you
for all you've done for us.
I can get us
out of the country.
That's very kind.
but I'm sure we can
muddle through on our own.
Anywhere in the shade up here
would be fine.
[ Indistinct conversations ]
I fear I've disappointed you.
The deal was for us
to actually catch the criminals
on the Blacklist.
and now Wujing is as good
as halfway to Beijing.
I don't think so.
Is everything okay?
We're fine.
[ Sirens wail ]
[ Tires screech ]
[ Indistinct shouting ]
[ Guns cocking ]
Man: Move! Move!
Let me see your hands!
Get out! Get out!
Get out!
- Up on the car! - Man: The package is secure.
Suspect in custody now.
Luli can stay with me.
Dembe will take you
wherever you need to go.
You didn't have to kill him.
I believe I will always do
whatever I feel I have to do
to keep you alive.
[ Car door closes ]
I held up my end of the deal.
Now it's your turn.
You owe me an answer.
What's the question?
Why me?
Because of your father.
What does that mean?
Did you know my father?
Have the two of you
met somehow?
I wish the answer were as simple
as the question seems.
But the truth is. the question
isn't simple. either.
I share your frustration.
You act like we're the same.
You're wrong.
I have a life.
people who care about me.
But you...
this is all you have.
I have you.
You okay?
I'll live.
Look. I just wanted to say.
uh...
maybe I've had some doubts
about you.
Maybe I haven't done the best
job of keeping them to myself.
but what you did today
was good work.
Thanks.
If you didn't get that message
out when you did.
Henry Cho wouldn't be alive.
Whatever else
went down in there.
you should feel good
about that.
[ "Here With Me" plays ]
♪ Caught in a riptide
♪ I was searching
for the truth ♪
♪ there was a reason
♪ I collided into you
♪ calling your name
in the midnight hour ♪
♪ reaching for you
from the endless dream ♪
♪ so many miles between us now
♪ that you are
always here with me ♪
[ Door closes ]
You were right.
Liz Keen is hiding something.
I put a flag on her.
Any tests.
reports. or files --
anything she requests
gets sent to us first.
She brought a bullet and
a shell casing into ballistics.
At her level.
the results were classified.
But that's the full report.
This isn't just classified.
Any briefings on this homicide
include the Secretary
of Homeland Security.
Who else knows about this?
♪ Calling your name
in the midnight hour ♪
♪ reaching for you
from the endless dream ♪
♪ so many miles between us now
♪ that you are
always here with me ♪
♪ with me
[ indistinct conversations ]
Hey.
How are you?
Good.
Great.
Let me take this for you.
Everyone wanted to
be here for Tom.
Hey.
Everything go okay?
Fine.
Thank you.
Hey. can we. um. talk
for a second. pre-lasagna?
I just wanted to apologize
for this morning.
It's okay.
No. no. no. I was wrong.
It's your job.
and. uh. I understand
if there are certain secrets
that you have to keep right now.
and that's okay.
Because -- because
we'll survive. like always.
I just want you to --
I-I love you.
I got to see a man
about some lasagna.
[ Indistinct conversations ]
[ Laughter ]
Sync by GeirDM
www.addic7ed.com